<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cassava Disease Detection</string>
    <string name="str_header">Cassava Leaf Disease Detection</string>
    <string name="str_developer">RnD by Mr. Yogeshwar Upendra Shendye</string>
    <string name="str_dev_class">TYMCA</string>
    <string name="str_college">Student of Finolex Academy of Management and Technology</string>

    <string name="str_capture_btn_txt">Take picture</string>
    <string name="str_detect_btn_txt">Check the plant for disease</string>

    <string name="str_new_img">Capture new image of a crop</string>
    <string name="str_report">View Previous reports</string>

    <string name="str_btn_predict">Predict</string>
    <string name="str_btn_add_to_doc">Add to the report</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_reports">ViewReports</string>

    <string name="str_predicted">Label of the predicted image as per the model</string>
    <string name="str_disease_info">Information about the disease Cause of the disease Severity etc</string>
    <string name="str_treatment">Information about the treatment of the disease, preventive measures etc</string>

    <string name="str_cbb">Cassava Bacterial Blight (CBB)</string>
    <string name="str_cbb_info">
        Originally discovered in Brazil in 1912, the disease has followed cultivation of cassava across the world.
        Among diseases which afflict cassava worldwide, bacterial blight causes the largest losses in terms of yield.
    </string>
    <string name="str_cbb_cure">
        Several disease management techniques have been developed to control Cbb incidence and dissemination. Cultural
        practices have been used to decrease the incidence of the pathogen or delay the effect of the disease in the field.
        Pruning or total extirpation of infected plant tissue, weed removal, use of certified seeds, bacterial analysis of
        stem cuttings and crop rotation are used the most to limit the disease presence in the field.Transplantation of
        clones is the most common mode of propagation of this crop so the most important control of bacterial wilt of
        cassava is planting uninfected clones. In areas where bacterial wilt has not yet been established, it is important
        to raise a new crop from a meristem culture certifiably free of disease. In areas where the disease is already
        prevalent, great care should be taken to ensure clippings are taken from healthy plants and even then from the
        highly lignified portion at the base of cassava plants which appear healthy. Seeds are known to be able harbor the
        pathogen, but successful sanitation measures have been described. Infected seed immersed in water at 60 °C
        showed no sign of bacterial survival while the seed showed no reduction in germination potential.Furthermore,
        the sanitation of tools and big machinery are crucial to avoid the infection of healthy plants through mechanical
        inoculation. In cropping and crop rotation have both been implemented in cassava cultivation and have been
        successful.In the instance of crop rotation following an infected cassava crop, deep soil turnover is
        recommended and a period of six months should be observed before cassava is planted again; X.axonopodis is a
        poor soil survivor and does not sporulate so this time frame should clear crop fields of inoculum.
        It is also important to clear the field of weeds as X. axonopodis is known to survive much longer
        epiphytically on weeds than it does in soil.
    </string>

    <string name="str_cbsd">Cassava Brown Stake Disease</string>
    <string name="str_cbsd_info">
        CBSD is characterized by severe chlorosis and necrosis on infected leaves, giving them a yellowish, mottled
        appearance.Chlorosis may be associated with the veins, spanning from the mid vein, secondary and tertiary veins,
        or rather in blotches unconnected to veins. Leaf symptoms vary greatly depending on a variety of factors.
        The growing conditions (i.e. altitude, rainfall quantity), plant age, and the virus species account for these
        differences.Brown streaks may appear on the stems of the cassava plant. Also, a dry brown-black necrotic rot of
        the cassava tuber exists, which may progress from a small lesion to the whole root. Finally, the roots can become
        constricted due to the tuber rot, stunting growth.Typically the affected plants do not possess all of these
        characteristics, but those that are severely affected may. Farmers may be unaware of their infected cassava
        crops until they are harvested and see the tuber lesions because leaves are asymptomatic.The cassava mosaic
        virus (CMV) is another cassava virus that exhibits foliar symptoms similar to CBSD, but they are more obvious.
    </string>
    <string name="str_cbsd_cure">
        Management tools are still being explored for the control of CBSD, and progress has been slow.The development of
        cassava with resistance to both CMD and CBSD is needed.In a few cassava varieties, natural resistance has been
        found against UBCSV. Widespread distribution of germplasm of these varieties can reduce disease incidence on
        a large scale. Furthermore, screening for resistance in farmer-preferred cassava genotypes in Africa is crucial
        for effective CBSD control and management.
    </string>

    <string name="str_cgm">Cassava Green Mottle (CGM)</string>
    <string name="str_cgm_info">
        It is only known from cassava, and only from Choiseul (and possibly Malaita), nowhere else in the world. In the
        lab, several plant species have been infected with this virus; these species are known as "indicator" plants
        and are used to identify and characterise many kinds of viruses: Chenopodium, Nicotiana (tobacco), Phaseolus
        (French bean), Cucumis (cucumber), Ricinus (castor oil) and Solanum (potato). Interestingly, Ipomoea
        (sweetpotato) was also infected in these tests. But whether or not infection occurs in the field is unknown.
    </string>
    <string name="str_cgm_cure">
        Surveys carried out in Solomon Islands in the late 1970s failed to find the disease anywhere but on the island of
        Choiseul. It was not found in the nearby Shortland Islands. People on Choiseul were made aware of the disease and
        asked not to take cuttings to other islands. However, there are no laws restricting the movement of planting
        material between islands of the country, so compliance is voluntary. Choiseul is near the island of Bougainville in
        Papua New Guinea, and residents of both islands move between the two, but it is not known if the virus disease
        occurs in Bougainville.
    </string>

    <string name="str_cmd">Cassava Mosaic Disease (CMD)</string>
    <string name="str_cmd_info">
        CMD is caused by a virus belonging to the virus family, Geminiviridae, and could be transmitted through two ways:
        through stakes from infected cassava mother plants, or, through the whitefly vector – the insect, Bemisia tabaci.
        If infected, cassava plants display a number of symptoms including stunted growth, as well as mosaic, deformed,
        twisted, and smaller, leaves. Depending on a number of factors including cassava variety, virus isolate, age of
        the plant at the time of infection, and mode of infection, CMD-affected plants produce few or no roots. Infection
        through cuttings is known to be more damaging than infection through whiteflies.
    </string>
    <string name="str_cmd_cure">
        Control strategies for cassava mosaic disease include sanitation and plant resistance. In this case, sanitation
        means using cuttings from healthy plants to start with a healthy plot and maintaining that healthy plot by
        identifying unhealthy plants and immediately removing them. This strategy does not protect them from being
        inoculated by whiteflies, but research shows that the virus is more aggressive in plants infected from
        contaminated cuttings than by insect vectors. There are also specific varieties that fare better against
        some viruses than others, so plant resistance is possible.For example, hybrids that are a result of
        crossing cassava and other species, such as Manihot melanobasis and M. glaziovii, have been shown to have
        considerable resistance to CMV.
    </string>

    <string name="str_healthy">Healthy</string>
    <string name="str_healthy_info">
        The crop is healthy. It still requires some monitoring so that it will be safe from diseases even in the future.
    </string>
    <string name="str_healthy_cure">
        The crop is healthy. It still requires some monitoring so that it will be safe from diseases even in the future.
    </string>

    <string name="str_lbl_name">Category : </string>
    <string name="str_lbl_info">Information : </string>
    <string name="str_lbl_cure">Known treatments / preventive measures : </string>
    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string name="hello_world">Hello Square World!</string>

</resources>